Ugh.
Guys, I like living in Skyrim.
Even if children point at me, and say;
"Kitty!"
My-my only problem is that it's illegal to worship the one true god, Talos.
Jaaaa.
Ja.
Yo.
This might be the mead talking,
but let's join the civil war, and kick out the empire
TONIGHT.
Sure. But I have to get to bed early, because
I have a dentist appointment.
And I'm in because I have no free will!
Nice!
Go Stormcloaks!
High King,
"KITTYYYYY!"
Uh... We'll go talk to the general.
Galmar, we would like to kill some imperials.
No civilians, though.
Okay. No more civilians, after this.
Okay, fine. We're already here, a couple more civilians.
Ugh. My back hurts,
I'm drenched in sweat,
and I'm out of booze.
I'd better get a city for this!
On behalf of the sons and daughters of Skyrim,
take this token of our appreciation of your service.
STUDDED ARMOUR!?
THAT'S IT!?
Okayyy!
This is fine.
I'm... SUPER fine.
I got to serve Skyrim.
And now... Now I get to worship in peace!
NO!
No, I'm not happy about this! Not happy at all!
Lafe? "Ja."
Sven? "Jaaaaaaaa?"
Let's execute the high king!
Should've given me a watch or something.
Now, I'm High King. And I'm not gonna be a tyrant.
[Excessively brief pause]
I've changed my mind.
Because it's weird that we had to fight all those battles to worship Talos...
While those other temples had to fight nothing! Right, Sven?
I am a scientologist.
Exactly.
Let's arrest every priest.
Yaaaay! Now people will be healed in the temple of Talos,
Marry in the temple of Talos,
Learn about intercourse from U n c l e T a l o s ,
Skyrim is great again!
But other provinces still worship all the divines.
Which is fine.
Each to his own.
No...
Wait...
I just had a completely new, revolutionary idea.
Other people shouldn't be allowed to have a different religion than me!
Pekka, is there a word for when you politely ask someone to change their ways?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Then I shall call it...
A CRUSADE!
Guys, we're gonna do a little bit of friendly-neighbor-crusading.
There's the Cyrodiil border guard!
Make them breathe way more less!
We made it across the border!
From here on out, only kill
ANYONE.
They're all heretics, especially children.
There's Bruma! Burn it to the ground!
TALOS VULT!
(t...talos vult.)
With us causing this much chaos, soon the Emperor will show up with his army.
"Is that him?"
No. He's in the Imperial-
...Yeah. That's him.
What in Oblivion is he doing here?
WHAT? Forty mistresses?
I'm impressed! But you still have to die, pagan.
You'll convert and give me Cyrodiil?
That's disappointing.
Still...
The province is ours!
Yeah!
Skyrim!
To Oblivion with Oblivion!
Wh... what do we do now?
Anyone got any ideas?
"I know a lizard!"
O... okay. Do you want to teach our Argonian friend that Talos is the only way?
That Skyrim is the best?
"Vittu! I prefer Morrowind."
Pekka, you are...
absolutely right!
We need to march East, to show those Morrowind fanboys
that us Skyriminos are not just a bunch of CASUALS.
Let's go.
These giant mushrooms means no-one starves,
and no-one gets fat.
Where were we?
Ah, right. The crusade.
Talos Vult! Crush these Dunmers.
And their way-better customization options!
They can't even scream, because they're not voice-acted
by five different people.
"What do you want to do with the old King?"
We shall sacrifice him to the Volcano God,
Talos.
So he can be judged by the death god...
Also Talos.
Uuuugh, what were the words again?
Fus... fus ro
dah?
Now! Let us return to Windhelm
before the bar closes.
No!
No!!
In what kind of dark fantasy universe does a bar close at 1:00?
"Did you see those warriors from Hammerfell?
They've got a bar that closes at 3:00!"
Guys!
I just had an idea.
We come in peace!
Just hand over all your liquor, and your entire province!
Great night, guys.
Daedra! It's 4:00 in the morning!
I gotta get back!
"We're going to High Rock!"
Nice. Keep... spreading the word of Talos.
I feel like I've forgotten some...one
that might be mad about us spreading our religion like this.
Eeegh, I'm sure it's nothing.
Aaah... Mehrunes' balls, my head.
What happened last night?
I had a couple of beers...
...went to piss...
...then I united Tamriel.
Talos-damn it.
A letter for me?
From the Calamari Dominion?
"Dear High King Kitty..."
ugh...
Every time.
"W-T-F, Brocephilon? You broke our law!"
"We're gonna war you now, DUDE!"
Uh-oh.
AH! They're already here!
Look at that discipline!
We'll be fine, as long as we have our greatest fighter, Lafe.
Where is he?
"His dentist appointment."
We're outmatched, and outnumbered.
"I know a Japanese guy!"
What's a Japane... and he's gone.
Lovely.
Let's do this.
For the Skyrim!
We're losing this battle, but I can't let my men down.
Where are you, Sven?
If you were here, we'd be losing a couple of seconds slower.
(in the distance)
"I am here!"
What.
By.
The.
Divine?
Sven knows Godzilla!
And he's coming to help us!
And this video was so lore-friendly...
They're retreating!
We saved Skyrim!
Let's go to Candlehearth Hall!
I'm buying the first round...
For myself!
I might like ruling Skyrim.
Think I've had enough for tonight, though.
Ahh, one more can't hurt.
Ah! Fuck!
My liver!
Ah, Daedra.
I'm dead.
So this is Sovngarde.
Oh my god! It's God!
Hello, Talos.
Are you the one, true Divine?
"No?"
Oh.
Well, I guess you have to die, then, heretic!